OSCAR VARGAS

BUSINESS ADMINISTRATOR

CONTACT

+57 3182448213 oavargasu@unal.edu.co

REFERENCES

DAVID BASTIDAS

LOGISTIC COORDINATOR CEMEX 3123225110

ARNULFO ORTEGA

MANAGER - BANCO AGRARIC

PROFILE

Business Administrator from the National University of Colombia with experience in the financial and commercial field. Additionally I speak the Portuguese language. Great skill in the Google suite (Google Sheets, Data Studio, Documents etc). Skills in handling Office tools, mainly handling Excel. Interested in expanding my knowledge in the field of Business Intelligence. Always willing to work as a team and be in continuous learning

EXPERIENCE

REVENUE ASSOCIATE BRAZIL

AC NIELSEN COLOMBIA | Aug 2019 - Current job

- Continuous review, monitoring and approval of Evidence of delivery of Marketing Services and Purchase Orders together with the Brazilian sales team. Revenue recognition based on review of POs
- Support in the automatic reporting of KPIs from the Commercial and Share Service Center team. Accounting closure of Unbilled and Deferred accounts.
- Making reconciliations, reports, reports and analyzes, with focus on automation and process improvement.

COLLECTION ASSOCIATE LATAM

AC NIELSEN COLOMBIA | Jan 2018 - JUL 2019

- Dashboards for portfolio risk management
- Creation of automated and integrated format with SAP tools for projection of Free Cash Flow figures to support executive decisions.
- Collection management of clean and aging portfolios greater than 360 days. (Clients: P&G, Ambev, Nestlé, Unilever, etc.)
- Focus on continuous process improvement.
- Reconciliation of AR accounts.

EDUCATION

BUSINESS ADMINISTRATOR FROM NATIONAL UNIVERSITY OF COLOMBIA

| 2013 - 2019

SKILLS

- Advanced level in Portuguese and English language.
- SAP
- Salesforce
- Google Suite (Scripts) and Office Suite (Macros)
- Basic handling of R and SQL
- Comminucation skills and disposition for teamwork